董卓主演脱口秀
怎么了，约翰·乔丹？
What's up, John Jordan?
今晚我们有很多东西要聊。
Well, we got so much to talk about tonight.
特朗普从加拿大偷偷溜走了。
Trump makes an Irish exit from Canada.
我得去华盛顿参加美国历史上最盛大的
I had to DC to crash the most tremendous birthday
生日派对。
bash in American history.
作家詹姆斯·帕特森
And the author, James Patterson,
将和他的合著者比尔·克林顿一起来到今晚的节目。
will be here along with his co-author, Bill Clinton tonight.
好吧？
OK?
那么，我们来说说今天的头条新闻。
So, let's get into the headline.
这本来应该是特朗普大展身手的一周。
Now, this is supposed to be study of broad week for Trump.
而且事情开始时确实非常顺利。
And things started out oh, so well.
他优雅地到达了G7峰会，
He arrived at the G7 competently,
从树林中走出来，就像《黄金单身女郎》的
strolling out of the woods like a contestant
参赛者，或者是个刮了毛的大脚怪，你懂的？
on the Golden Bachelorette, or a shaved sassquatch, you know?
看你怎么理解了。
You see what you want to see.
这次G7对特朗普来说很重要，
Now, this is an important G7 for Trump,
因为他必须证明自己有能力和决心
because he had to prove that he had the discipline
去修复全球经济，在他
and wherewithal to fix the global economy after he
搞砸了全球经济之后。
f**ked up the global economy.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
他差点就成功了。
He almost nailed it.
我们都认识英国的伟大首相，
We all know the great prime minister of the UK,
我们刚刚签署了一份文件。
and we just signed a document.
我想到了这个替换。
Mrs. Swap, I thought about that.
你在文件方面表现很差。
You went very poor at documents.
你没有赢得反收购。
You didn't win the anti-acquiring.
别担心，别担心。
Don't worry, don't worry.
贸易协定有五秒钟法则。
There's a five-second rule with trade agreements.
特朗普还是完全可以把那些文件"吃掉"的。
Trump's still totally good to eat those documents.
我知道你们这些黑粉会取笑他们，
And I know some of you haters are going to make fun of them,
但特朗普掉文件不是意外。
but Trump didn't drop the papers by accident.
这是4D象棋走法，为了看看
It was a 4D chess move to check out
英国首相会不会被甩掉。
the British prime ministers, but don't get dumped.
但在特朗普能够签署或掉下任何其他贸易协定之前，
But before Trump could sign and or drop any other trade deals,
他决定撤退了。
he decided to peace out.
昨夜，特朗普总统突然转身，
Overnight, President Trump with an abrupt about face,
宣布他要缩短
announcing he's cutting short his trip
在加拿大G7峰会的行程，
to the G7 summit in Canada,
急速赶回白宫。
racing back to the White House instead.
我必须回去，非常重要。
I have to be back very important.
我只想感谢我们伟大的...
I want to just thank our great-nose.
但你可能看到了我看到的。
But you're probably seeing what I see.
我必须回去。
And I have to be back.
我们都知道这是什么情况，对吧？
We all know what this is, right?
你在参加活动。
You're at an event.
你必须急忙回家因为出了什么事。
You have to rush home because something came up.
看，我理解。
Look, I get it.
我们都不喜欢在陌生地方上厕所。
None of us like to poop in an unfamiliar place.
有时候当你面临大战时，
Sometimes when you have a big matchup coming up,
你就是需要主场优势。
you just need that home-field advantage.
我理解，唐纳德。
I understand, Donald.
但当然，唐纳德·特朗普急忙回家到华盛顿的
But of course, the real reason Donald Trump rushed home
真正原因是处理以色列和伊朗之间的战争。
to Washington was to deal with the war between Israel and Iran.
大问题是，他急忙回家
And the big question was, was he rushing home
是为了帮助谈判结束战争
to help negotiate an end to the war
还是把美国拖入战争？
or to bring America into the war?
这是一个国家能做出的最重要决定。
It's the most important decision a nation can make.
而且是一个我们在过去10年、20年、30年、40年都搞砸了的决定。
And one, that we've whiffed on for the last 10, 20, 30, 40.
不管了。重点是，
It doesn't matter. The point is,
知道总统有一个清晰一致的计划
it'd be really reassuring to know that the president
会很令人安心。
has a clear and consistent plan.
所以总统先生，您是在寻求战争还是停火？
So Mr. President, are you looking for war or ceasefire?
寻求停火？
What about looking for a ceasefire?
谁说我在寻求停火？
And say I was looking for a ceasefire.
哦，该死。好吧。
Oh, shit. OK.
他不是在寻求停火。
He's not looking for a ceasefire.
我们在寻求比停火更好的东西。
We're looking at better than ceasefire.
哦，太好了。
Oh, great.
是的。比停火更好。
Yeah. Better than a ceasefire.
停火升级版。
ceasefire plus.
太棒了。
That's great.
我讨厌看广告。
I hate watching ads.
太好了。
That's wonderful.
这是好消息。
This is good news.
我很高兴你要和伊朗谈判。
I'm glad you're going to negotiate with Iran.
我不知道。我不太想谈判。
I don't know. I'm not too much in a book to negotiate.
好吧。行吧。
OK. All right.
没心情。好吧。
Not in the mood. OK.
总统对谈判没兴趣。
The president's not vibrant on negotiations then.
所以是战争。
So it's war.
因为除了您，总统先生，谁还不愿意谈判？
Because who wouldn't negotiate besides you, Mr. President?
他正在考虑派副总统
He's considering sending the vice president
去和伊朗人谈判。
to negotiate with the Iranians.
我觉得这太棒了。
I think this is fantastic.
JD·万斯是谈判的绝佳选择。
JD Vance is a great choice to negotiate.
伊朗人会同意任何条件，只要能让他滚蛋。
The Iranians will agree to anything to get him the f*** out of there.
你知道吗？
You know what?
这对和平很好。
And it's great for peace.
因为如果特朗普在谈判，听起来我们不会
Because if Trump is negotiating, it sounds like we're not
很快就把德黑兰夷为平地。
going to flatten Tehran anytime soon.
总统警告伊朗首都的所有人逃跑。
The president warned everyone in Iran's capital city to flee.
发帖说每个人都应该立即撤离伊朗，
Posting everyone should immediately evacuate to Iran
没有额外解释。
with no additional explanation.
你知道吗？我需要一些额外的解释。
You know what? I could use some additional explanation.
总统先生，我比以往任何时候都更困惑。
Mr. President, I am more confused than ever.
请用一条清晰的推文总结您的解释。
Please just sum up your explanation in one clean tweet.
特朗普总统刚刚发布了针对伊朗的新评论。
President Trump has just posted new comments directed at Iran.
我们确切知道所谓的最高领袖藏在哪里。
We know exactly where the so-called Supreme Leader is hiding.
他是个容易的目标，但在那里是安全的。
He is an easy target, but is safe there.
我们不会干掉他，然后在括号里，
We are not going to take him out and then in parentheses,
杀死，至少现在不会。
kill at least not for now.
好吧。
OK.
所以我们知道阿亚图拉在哪里，但他是安全的。
So we know where the Iatola is, but he's safe.
我们可以杀死他，但我们不会。
We could kill him, but we won't.
现在不会，也许以后。
For now, maybe later.
下次《黄金单身女郎》会揭晓，好吗？
We'll find out next on the Golden Bachelorette, OK?
一条推文怎么能有六种不同的立场？
How does one tweet and have six different positions?
我是说，显然我们听特朗普总统讲话
I mean, clearly, we're not going to get any clarity
不会得到任何澄清。
from listening to President Trump.
也许他内圈的其他人
Maybe other people in his inner circle
能够阐明美国的立场。
can shed some light on America's position.
塔克·卡尔森，总统的大力支持者。
Tucker Carlson, huge supporter of the president.
你对这场战争怎么看？
What do you think of the war?
我只是不希望我的国家被另一场战争
I just don't want my country to be further weakened or destroyed
进一步削弱或摧毁。
by another one of these wars.
如果25年后你还连不上点，
And boy, if you can't connect the dots after 25 years,
那该死的。
the ****.
你要么太蠢了不配参与这个对话，
You're either too dumb to participate in the conversation
要么就是个不在乎的骗子。
or you're just a liar who doesn't care.
哇。
Wow.
我是说，塔克，他自从WNBA
I mean, Tucker, he hasn't been mistrustraught
变得受欢迎后就没这么心烦意乱过。
since the WNBA got popular.
好吧，总统先生，我希望您理解
OK, Mr. President, I hope you understand
塔克·卡尔森在说什么。
what Tucker Carlson is saying.
我不知道塔克·卡尔森在说什么。
I don't know what Tucker Carlson is saying.
让他去搞个电视网络说出来，这样人们才会听。
Let him go get a television network and say it so that people listen.
谢谢。
Thank you.
哦，天哪。
Oh, snap.
特朗普就像在说：去电视上说吧，婊子。
Trump's like, go on TV and say it, you bitch.
没错。
That's right.
你不能，因为你被福克斯新闻踢了，
You can't because you got kicked off Fox News
因为你撒谎说我赢了2020年选举，
for lying about me winning the 2020 election,
对此我很感激，婊子。
which I appreciate, you bitch.
所以是的，特朗普和塔克不在一个频道上。
So yes, Trump is not on the same page as Tucker.
他似乎也与其他一些顶级MAGA人士有分歧。
And he seems to be at odds with some of the other top magamines as well.
美国人民被洗脑了，相信
The American people have been brainwashed into believing
美国必须参与这些海外战争
that America has to engage in these foreign wars
我们才能生存。
in order for us to survive.
这绝对不是真的。
And it's absolutely not true.
我的天啊。
Oh my God.
我不敢相信我同意马乔里·泰勒·格林的观点。
I can't believe I'm a green with marjorie Taylor Greene.
我和自己开战了。
I'm not war with myself.
这不对。
And this can't be right.
继续播放这段视频。
Keep playing the clip.
我肯定能找到什么和她不同的观点。
I'm sure I'll find something to disagree with her on.
他们不想听政治。
They don't want to hear about politics.
他们想要能够负担得起食物，
They want to be able to afford food,
他们想要能够负担得起汽油。
and they want to be able to afford gas.
他们只想在生活中开心一次。
And they just want to have fun for once in their life.
他们想要开心。
They want to have fun.
是的，我仍然同意她的观点，在他们的生活中开心一次。
Yes, I still agree with her for once in their life.
美国人只想开心。
Americans just want to have fun.
我不想要战争。
I don't want to war.
我想要跳舞。
I want to dance.
虽然你知道吗，我很确定美国人确实知道
Although you know what, I'm pretty sure Americans do know
如何不管国际冲突都能开心。
how to have fun regardless of international conflicts.
我从来没收到过这样的短信：嘿，兄弟，
I've never gotten a text saying, hey, bro,
南中国海有领土争端，
territorial dispute in the South China Sea,
烧烤取消了。
barbecue's canceled.
所以，看起来特朗普没有听取
So, doesn't seem like Trump is listening
他党内反战派的意见。
to the anti-war wing of his party.
也许他会听取自己政府内反战派的意见，
Maybe he'll listen to the anti-war wing of his own administration,
比如图尔西·加巴德，他的国家情报总监。
like Tulsi Gabbard, his own director of national intelligence.
图尔西·加巴德三月份作证说情报部门说
Tulsi Gabbard testified at March that the intelligence community said
伊朗没有在制造核武器。
Iran wasn't building a nuclear weapon.
她说的，我认为他们很接近拥有那种武器。
What she said, I think they were very close to having that weapon.
笑声
LAUGHTER
这就是任命不合格疯子到你团队的好处。
This is the benefit of appointing unqualified, crazy people to your team.
你总是可以说，你知道她有多疯多不合格吗？
You could always be like, do you know how crazy ununqualified she is?
我不在乎她说什么。
I don't care what she said.
所以，特朗普与他党内的反战派发生冲突，
So, Trump is beefing with the anti-war wing of his party
并且无视来自自己内阁的情报，
and dismissing intelligence from his own cabinet,
那些显示伊朗实际上没有制造核武器的情报。
showing that Iran is not actually building nukes.
这看起来确实倾向于"让我们来第三次世界大战"的方向。
It certainly seems to be leaning in a Let's Do a World War III direction.
奇怪的是，最终的确认可能是披萨。
Weirdly enough, the final confirmation might be pizza.
根据X上一个叫"五角大楼披萨报告"的账户，
According to an account on X called the Pentagon Pizza Report,
五角大楼附近几乎所有的披萨店
nearly all pizza establishments nearby the Pentagon
都经历了巨大的活动激增。
have experienced a huge surge in activity.
原因是当美国军事人员面临国家紧急状态时，
Here's why when U.S. military personnel face a national emergency,
他们工作到深夜，不能离开办公桌。
they work late into the night and can't leave their desks.
周四晚上8点57分，五角大楼披萨报告报告
At 8.57 p.m. Thursday, the Pentagon Pizza Report reported
距离五角大楼最近和第二近的达美乐
that the closest and second closest dominoes to the Pentagon
流量激增。
had surged in traffic.
哦，我的天啊，我们要开战了！
Oh, my God, we're going to war!
或者五角大楼的每个人都同时离婚了！
Or everyone at the Pentagon just got divorced at the same time!
看，我不知道事情会怎么结束，
Look, I don't know how things are going to end,
但看起来趋势很糟糕。
but it seems like they're trending in a bad direction.
不过我会说这个。
I will say this, though.
如果你在选举日后告诉我，在特朗普总统任期的四个月内，
If you told me after election day that within four months of Trump's presidency,
我会盯着达美乐披萨追踪器
I'd be staring at a dominoes pizza tracker
来判断我们是否会进入人类的最后一场战争。
to figure out if we're going to enter the final war of mankind.
我会说，这听起来很对。
I'd have said, that's about right.
更多关于与伊朗即将开战的信息，我们在五角大楼外
For more on the pending war with Iran, we go live outside the Pentagon
连线我们的迈克尔·科斯塔。
with our own Michael Kosta.
迈克尔！
Michael!
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
迈克尔。
Michael.
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
我很好奇，迈克尔。
I'm curious, Michael.
最新情况是什么？
What is the latest?
乔丹，这是一个微妙复杂的情况，
Jordan, this is a nuanced and complicated situation
唯一的解决方案是美国与伊朗进行数十年的全面战争。
and the only solution is for America to enter a decades-long total war with Iran.
毫无疑问。
Make no mistake.
美国军队需要扎根，系好安全带，
The U.S. military needs to dig in, buckle down,
拿起一些迈克K的肉食爱好者披萨配特制酸酱，
pick up some Mikey K's meatlovers pizzas with extra tangy sauce
准备迎接最坏的情况。
and prepare for the worst.
抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你刚才说的关于准备最坏情况的后半句是什么？
What was that last part you said about preparing for the worst?
是的。
Yes.
我们可能也需要新的征兵。
We'll probably need a new draft, too.
数百万身体健康的年轻人准备为美国而战，
Millions of able-bodied young men ready to fight for America
大吃特吃迈克K的水牛鸡肉至尊"妈妈咪呀"披萨 （注：mam-mamiya是mama mia的变形，模仿意大利口音）
and chow down on Mikey K's buffalo chicken supreme mam-mamiya
配免费45盎司激浪红码汽水，就像奶奶做的一样。 （注：这里语法有误，应该是"just like Nona used to make"，但他说成了"used to me"，可能是口误或故意搞笑）
with a free 45-ounce Mountain Dew Code red, just like Nona used to me.
笑声
LAUGHTER
什么，你开披萨店吗？
What, do you own a pizza parlor?
你想从战争中牟利吗？
Are you trying to profiteer from a war?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
我在附近的一家披萨店有小额投资，
I have a small investment in a pizza place nearby
我也在那里当经理和服务员，
that I also manage and busboy at,
但这绝不影响我的公正分析。
but that in no way affects my impartial analysis.
我看过证据，我们必须与伊朗开战。
I've looked at the evidence and we have to go to war against Iran.
可能再次与伊拉克，绝对与印度。
Possibly Iraq again and definitely India.
笑声
LAUGHTER
印度做了什么？
What did India do?
嗯，他们是地区超级大国，乔丹。
Well, they're a regional superpower, Jordan.
他们威胁着我们的生存。
They're a threat to our survival.
现在，他们的军事领导人在策划对付我们，日夜工作，
Right now, their military leaders are plotting against us working day and night,
订购美味的外卖。
ordering delicious taker.
迈克尔，你在印度有披萨店吗？
Michael, do you have a pizza place in India?
绝对没有。
Absolutely not.
那是一家小型坦杜里厨房，叫"无人能及"。
It's a small, tandoori kitchen called second to non.
笑声
LAUGHTER
任何订单都免费芒果拉西，就像奶奶做的一样。
Free mango lassi with every any order, just like Nona used to make.
嘿，科斯塔，拜托，老兄。这太疯狂了。
Hey, Costa, come on, man. That's, this is crazy.
我知道。任何订单，乔丹，没有最低消费。
I know. With any order, Jordan, there is no minimum.
不，不，疯狂的是你想要发动第三次世界大战
No, no, what's crazy is you're trying to start World War III
这样你就能，什么，卖劣质外卖？
so you can, what, sell bad takeout?
劣质外卖。
Bad takeout.
你怎么敢？
How dare you?
艺术酸辣酱是新德里的话题。
Art Chutney is the talk of New Delhi.
我想我搞不懂他们在说什么。
I assume I can't figure out what they're saying.
但是，有什么大不了的？
But, what's the big deal?
国防承包商可以为了利润
Defense contractors can go to our nation
把我们国家拖入无休止的无意义战争，
into endless pointless wars for profit,
但奶奶科斯塔就不能分一杯羹？
but Nona, Costa, can't get a taste?
看，你们都很坏。
Look, you're all bad.
美国人不想要战争。
Americans don't want war.
有没有办法从和平中赚钱，
Isn't there a way to make money off peace
这样世界就能和谐共处？
so the world can live in harmony?
国际关系没那么简单，乔丹。
International relations aren't that simple, Jordan.
两个完全相对的国家无法克服
Two nations, their total opposites can't overcome
他们的文化差异，
their cultural differences,
在神奇宁静的完美融合中团结。
uniting in a perfect blend of magical serenity.
唯一存在的地方
The only place that that exists
就是我们新的美味寿司卷饼。
is in our new delicious sushi taco.
笑声
LAUGHTER
正如我奶奶常说的，
As my Nona used to say,
嗯，我们，空尼基哇。
mmm, as we, Konichiwa.
哦，是的，我们走了。
Oh, yeah, we get out of here.
迈克尔·科斯塔，各位。
Michael Costa, everyone.
音乐
MUSIC